Finding Aid for the Alan Rich Papers, 1960-2010 LSC.1975
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 6: Media, 1950-2009
  - Stein, Leonard: Leonard Stein Remembers: Conversations with Piano Spheres Pianists. 1 CD, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Stone, Dorothy: None But the Lonely Flute CD, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Unlabeled 7" Reels (2), undated (Box 20)
  - Unlabeled 7" Reels (5), undated (Box 24)
  - Verrett, Shirley: Philharmonic Hall performance, 7" Reel, 1963 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous 7" Reels (38 reels), undated (Box 23)
    Contains mostly unlabeled 7" reels, but also includes compositions by Robert Erickson, interviews with Pierre Boulez, and performances by the Los Angeles Philharmonic.
  - Audio cassettes (27 cassettes), undated (Box 17)
  - Audio cassettes, 1950-1999 (Box 19)
    Includes the remaining Freeman Musicales recordings, Rich's work from the Pacifica Tape Library, and various Rich interviews and radio programs including Pablo Casals, Mauricio Kagel, Anthony Davis, and Ned Rorem. Includes part of the Romantic Art Song radio program (scripts are in the Writing series).
  - Audio cassettes (22 cassettes), 1972-1999 (Box 16)
    Recordings of interviews and radio programs. Highlights include Rich's interviews with Maria Callas.
  - Audio cassettes, 1982-1987 (Box 18)
    Includes archival recordings of the Freeman Musicales, salons featuring major composers and hosted by Rich with philanthropist Betty Freeman in Freeman's home. Also includes recordings of works played at the salons, either live or from recordings. Notable composers include Steve Reich, Pauline Oliveros, Milton Babbitt, Conlon Nancarrow, Terry Riley, and others.
  - Commercial recordings, 1986-1999 (Box 24)
    A vast majority of the recordings consist of recordings by Bela Bartok, but also includes other "B" composers such as Amy Beach.
    Includes 36 CDs and 1 zip disk.